<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DarshanApp</string>
    <string name="ghewar_title">Ghewar</string>
    <string name="ghewar_body">Ghevar is a North Indian cuisine sweet traditionally associated with the Teej Festival.
        It is disc-shaped sweet cake made with all-purpose flour and soaked in sugar syrup.
        There are many varieties of Ghevar, including plain, mawa and malai ghevar.</string>
    <string name="dalbatti_title">Dal Batti</string>
    <string name="dalbatti_body">Dal baati is an Indian dish comprising dal and baati.
        It is popular in Rajasthan, Uttar Pradesh and Madhya Pradesh. Dal is prepared using tuvaar dal,
        chana dal, mung dal, moth dal, or urad dal.</string>
    <string name="golgappa_title">Pani Puri</string>
    <string name="pavbhaji_title">Pav Bhaji</string>
    <string name="rawatkachori_title">Kachori By Rawat</string>
    <string name="golgappa_body">Panipuri is a common street snack in several regions of the Indian subcontinent. It consists of a round, hollow puri, fried crisp and filled with a mixture of flavored water, tamarind chutney, chili, chaat masala, potato, onion or chickpeas.</string>
    <string name="pavbhaji_body">Pav bhaji is a fast food dish from India, consisting of a thick vegetable curry, fried and served with a soft bread roll.</string>
    <string name="rawatkachori_body">Kachori is a spicy snack, originating from the Indian subcontinent, and common in places with Indian diaspora and other South Asian diaspora, such as Trinidad and Tobago, Guyana, and Suriname.</string>
    <string name="history_title">Rajasthan</string>
    <string name="history_body">
        Rajasthani cuisine (Hindi: राजस्थानी खाना) was influenced by both the war-like lifestyles of its inhabitants and the availability
        of ingredients in this arid region.[1] Food that could last for several days and could be eaten without heating was
        preferred. Scarcity of water and fresh green vegetables have all had their effect on the cooking. It is also known for its snacks
        like Bikaneri Bhujia, Mirchi Bada and Pyaaj Kachori. Other famous dishes include Bajre ki roti (millet bread) and Lashun ki chutney
        (hot garlic paste), Mawa Kachori from jodhpur, Alwar ka mawa, Malpauas from pushkar and Rassgollas from Bikaner, "paniya"and "gheriya"
        from Mewar.[1] Originating for the Marwar region of the state is the concept Marwari Bhojnalaya, or vegetarian restaurants, today
        found in many part of India, which offer vegetarian food of the Marwari people.</string>
    <string name="ashok_title">Hotel Ashok Palace</string>
    <string name="ashok_body">\nOpen 9:00AM - 11:00PM \n\nAddress : D-2, Railway Station Road, Near Metro Pillar No.
        148, Gopalbari, Jaipur, Rajasthan 302001 \n\nMobile : 080031 25730</string>
    <string name="indanapalace_title">Hotel Indiana Palace</string>
    <string name="narainapalace_title">Naraina Palace</string>
    <string name="radissonblu_title">Hotel Radisson Palace</string>
    <string name="rambagpalace_title">Rambagh Palace By Taj Group</string>
    <string name="indianapalace_body">\nAddress : Janpath, Ambedkar Nagar, Tonk Phatak, Jaipur, Rajasthan 302015
        \n\nMobile : 0141 510 2040 \n\nDinner and Lunch availabe on Demand</string>
    <string name="narainapalace_body">\nWebsite : hotelnarainniwas.com \n\nAddress : A-8, National Highway 8,
        Gajsinghpur, Jaipur, Rajasthan \n\nMobile : 094603 17743</string>
    <string name="radissonblu_body">\nBright accommodations in a modern venue with a rooftop pool,
        a restaurant and 2 bars.\n\nAddress : Plot No. 5 - 6, Airport Plaza. Tonk Road, Jai Jawan-2,
        Choti Chopad, Chandrakala Colony, Mata colony, Jaipur, Rajasthan 302018 \n\nMobile : 0141 669 8888 \n\nWebsite : radissonblu.com</string>
    <string name="rambagpalace_body">\nGrand hotel in a converted 19th-century palace, plus a spa, genteel dining and
        meditation classes. \n\nAddress : Bhawani Singh Road, Rambagh, Jaipur, Rajasthan 302005 \n\nWebsite : taj.tajhotels.com \n\nMobile : 0141 238 5700</string>
    <string name="amber_title">Amer Fort</string>
    <string name="amber_body">\nOpen from 8:00AM - 6:00PM \n\nAmer Fort is a fort located in Amer,
        Rajasthan, India. Amer is a town with an area of 4 square kilometres located 11 kilometres from Jaipur,
        the capital of Rajasthan. Located high on a hill, it is the principal tourist attraction in Jaipur.</string>
    <string name="birlamandir_title">Birla Temple</string>
    <string name="birlamandir_body">Birla Mandir refers to different Hindu temples or Mandirs built by the Birla family,
        in different cities. All these temples are magnificently built, some of them in white marble or in sandstone.</string>
    <string name="galataji_title">Galataji Temple</string>
    <string name="galataji_body">Galtaji is an ancient Hindu pilgrimage about 10 km away from Jaipur, in the Indian state of Rajasthan.
        The site consists of a series of temples built into a narrow crevice in the ring of hills that surrounds Jaipur.</string>
    <string name="hawamahal_title">Hawa Mahal</string>
    <string name="hawalmahal_body">\nAddress : Hawa Mahal Rd, Badi Choupad, J.D.A. Market, Kanwar Nagar, Jaipur, Rajasthan 302002
        \n\nHeight: 15 m \n\nHawa Mahal is a palace in Jaipur, India. It is constructed of red and pink sandstone.
        The palace sits on the edge of the City Palace, Jaipur, and extends to the zenana, or women's chambers.</string>
    <string name="jantarmantar_title">Jantar Mantar</string>
    <string name="jantarmantar_body">\nUNESCO World Heritage Site inscription: 2010 \n\nHours : Opens 9AM \n\nAddress: Gangori Bazaar, J.D.A. Market,
        Kanwar Nagar, Jaipur, Rajasthan 302002 \n\nThe Jantar Mantar monument in Jaipur, Rajasthan is a collection of nineteen architectural astronomical
        instruments built by the Rajput king Sawai Jai Singh II, and completed in 1734.</string>
    <string name="food">Food</string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="sights">Sights</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
</resources>
